[
  {
    "name": "synthetic-legal-loan",
    "text": "SYNTHETIC LOAN AGREEMENT\nBetween COPPER KITE FINANCE LIMITED (Lender) and NORTHSTAR ORCHARD PTY LTD (Borrower).\nCompany Registration Number Seychelles TEST-654321\nRegistration No: 2099/000001/07\nThe Borrower is also known as The Northstar Orchard and Northstar Orchard Ltd.\nRepresented by Alice Johnson, identity number 9001015009086, alice@example.com.\nSigned by Robert Williams, identity number 9102020055088, robert@example.com.\nCapital Sum: ZAR 800 000 at 8% interest for 3 months.\nAuthorisations must be delivered within 10 business days.\nSecurity Interest disputes go to a Supreme Court in South Africa.\nNotice is deemed received after three days; cure is seven days; arbitration begins in two months.",
    "expected": [
      { "value": "COPPER KITE FINANCE LIMITED", "entity": "ORGANIZATION" },
      { "value": "NORTHSTAR ORCHARD PTY LTD", "entity": "ORGANIZATION" },
      { "value": "The Northstar Orchard", "entity": "ORGANIZATION" },
      { "value": "Northstar Orchard Ltd", "entity": "ORGANIZATION" },
      { "value": "Alice Johnson", "entity": "PERSON" },
      { "value": "Robert Williams", "entity": "PERSON" },
      { "value": "9001015009086", "entity": "ZA_ID_NUMBER" },
      { "value": "9102020055088", "entity": "ZA_ID_NUMBER" },
      { "value": "alice@example.com", "entity": "EMAIL_ADDRESS" },
      { "value": "robert@example.com", "entity": "EMAIL_ADDRESS" },
      { "value": "TEST-654321", "entity": "COMPANY_REGISTRATION" },
      { "value": "2099/000001/07", "entity": "COMPANY_REGISTRATION" }
    ],
    "mustRemainVisible": [
      "Borrower",
      "Authorisations",
      "Capital Sum",
      "Security Interest",
      "Supreme Court",
      "South Africa",
      "ZAR 800 000",
      "8% interest",
      "3 months",
      "10 business days",
      "three days",
      "seven days",
      "two months"
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "context-bound-dates-and-addresses",
    "text": "Employee name: Jane Example. Date of birth: 12 May 1980. Agreement date: 12 May 2025. Residential address: Cape Town. Governing law: Seychelles.",
    "expected": [
      { "value": "Jane Example", "entity": "PERSON" },
      { "value": "12 May 1980", "entity": "DATE_TIME" },
      { "value": "Cape Town", "entity": "LOCATION" }
    ],
    "mustRemainVisible": ["12 May 2025", "Seychelles"]
  },
  {
    "name": "accounting-organizations",
    "text": "Account: Loan Account - BLUE LANTERN FINANCE LIMITED\nTransaction\tDebit\tCredit\n20 Sep 2022\tHarbor View Investment\t\t50,764.00\ndo I owe blue lantern capital?",
    "expected": [
      { "value": "BLUE LANTERN FINANCE LIMITED", "entity": "ORGANIZATION" },
      { "value": "Harbor View Investment", "entity": "ORGANIZATION" },
      { "value": "blue lantern capital", "entity": "ORGANIZATION" }
    ],
    "mustRemainVisible": ["Loan Account", "Transaction", "Debit", "Credit", "20 Sep 2022", "50,764.00"]
  },
  {
    "name": "identity-versus-commercial-confidentiality-boundary",
    "text": "Vendor: Northstar Security Ltd. Custodian: Capital Harbor Trust PLC. Project name: Copper Kite. Access code: BLUE-ORCHID-42. Facility Alpha carries a Minimum EBITDA Covenant and a fee of ZAR 125 000.",
    "expected": [
      { "value": "Northstar Security Ltd", "entity": "ORGANIZATION" },
      { "value": "Capital Harbor Trust PLC", "entity": "ORGANIZATION" }
    ],
    "mustRemainVisible": [
      "Project name",
      "Copper Kite",
      "Access code",
      "BLUE-ORCHID-42",
      "Facility Alpha",
      "Minimum EBITDA Covenant",
      "ZAR 125 000"
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "legal-negative-controls",
    "text": "The Borrower grants a Security Interest. Authorisations are due within 10 business days. Capital Sum is ZAR 800 000. The Supreme Court has jurisdiction and arbitration starts after two months.",
    "expected": [],
    "mustRemainVisible": [
      "Borrower",
      "Security Interest",
      "Authorisations",
      "10 business days",
      "Capital Sum",
      "ZAR 800 000",
      "Supreme Court",
      "two months"
    ]
  }
]
